http://www.samcases.co.uk/privacy/

Contact
Get a FREE Quote!
Privacy Policy & Cookies
This privacy policy sets out how SAM Cases Ltd uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.
SAM Cases Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
SAM Cases Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
Privacy
SAM Cases Ltd (www.samcases.co.uk) takes your privacy seriously. We are registered under and comply with the Data Protection Act 1998.
1  SAM Cases Limited complies with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 when dealing with all data received from visitors to the site.
2  We only hold the data necessary to offer services provided on our website.
3  Data is only used for the purposes described in our entry on the Data Protection Register.
4  We only hold personal data for as long as necessary. Once data is no longer needed it is deleted from our files.
5  For administrative reasons email subscription data may be passed to and stored securely with third party service providers located outside the EEA (European Economic Area).
6  We regularly email website news and information updates to those customers who have specifically subscribed to our email service. All subscription emails sent by us contain clear information on how to unsubscribe from our email service.
7  We never sell, rent or exchange mailing lists.
8  We may however share commercial and technical data with our partners where a customer has accessed and used our website via a site belonging to one of our partners. However, such information will also be subject to our partners' privacy policies.
9  If you subscribe to our email service via a partner site, that partner may wish to send you details via email of other products and services, which may be of interest to you. However when you subscribe directly to our email service you will be asked whether or not you wish to receive such emails.
10  Please note that we only share data with partners that operate their own privacy policy.
11  In accordance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, we never send bulk unsolicited emails, (popularly known as Spam) to email addresses.
12  We may send emails to existing customers or prospective customers who have enquired or registered with us, regarding products or services directly provided by us.
13  All emails sent by us will be clearly marked as originating from us. All such emails will also include clear instructions on how unsubscribe from our email service and any future emails. Such instructions will either include a link to a page to unsubscribe or a valid email address to which you should reply, with unsubscribe as the email subject heading.
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) came into force on 25th May 2018. SAM Cases Limited would like to advise on what data we hold, how it is stored and how we use it.
1  We do not hold any of your personal data, only data relating to your order (e-mail address, name and invoice/delivery details). These are the details provided by you and are necessary to enable us to fulfil the contractual obligations of sale between us.
2  Any financial details provided to pay pro-forma invoices via credit card are destroyed immediately after payment has been authorised.
3  SAM Cases Limited take your privacy seriously and will only use this data to administer your account and to provide details or information that you have expressly requested. The data is stored securely within our servers and is protected using up-to-date security software and IT protection which contain firewalls.
4  Your data will be retained for 7 years after termination of our relationship, to comply with our statutory requirements.
5  SAM Cases Limited will never disclose your data to any third party or sell or transfer our e-mail database.
We trust you understand and should you need any clarification please feel free to contact us at any time to find out what details we may have for you.
Cookies
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. They are extremely common and most websites use them in order to improve your browsing experience. They allow the website to remember useful information such as what's in your shopping cart and whether you are currently logged in. Information provided by cookies can also help the website owner analyse your use of their website and this is an important aspect of being able to provide you with a better user experience. Cookies stay active for differing lengths of time depending on their purpose.
How our website uses cookies
Our website uses cookies to track use and allow customers to purchase from our website. Cookies keep track of the contents of your shopping cart during the checkout process which ensures that the items added to (or removed from) your cart are accurately stated when you go to pay.
Like many websites, we use Google Analytics to collect information about how visitors use our website and to identify any problems such as broken links. Google Analytics stores information about the pages of our website that you visit, how long you spend on our website, how you got here and what you clicked on. This helps us to improve our website. We do not store your personal information, so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.
Cookies are also used to measure the performance of our advertising campaigns when users click on our ads shown on networks such as Google. Please note that these cookies do NOT contain or pass any personal, confidential or financial information or any other information that could be used to identify individual visitors or customers purchasing from our website. We do not allow Google to share our data. Google provides more details on the Google privacy and cookie policy page.
Below is a list of the cookies that may be stored on your computer or mobile device when visiting our website. From time to time we may change this list as we introduce or remove functionality from our website. By using our website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your computer or device.
Name
Function
Expires
meerkat
When we have news that we wish to highlight, we show a notification bar along the bottom of the browser window. Inside this bar is a Close link which, when clicked, will make this bar disappear. The purpose of this cookie is to remember to keep the bar hidden so that it doesn't keep popping up as you browse different pages of the website.
When you close your browser
_ga
This cookie is used by Google Analytics to distinguish users and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form so that we can measure the number of visitors to our website.
2 years
_gat, _gid
These cookies operate in conjunction with _ga to collect information about how visitors use our website including how visitors arrived at the site and which pages they visited. The cookies collect information in a way that does NOT directly identify anyone. The information is collected to help us improve the site. _gat expires after 10 minutes.
1 day
ddfmcode
This cookie is necessary for the generation of the verify or 'Captcha' code at the bottom of contact forms. This is the series of letters and numbers that you are asked to type in when you fill in the form to prove that you are a human rather than a 'robot'.
1 hour
How do I change my cookie settings?
Cookies are normally enabled by default on your computer or mobile device. Without them, your experience on samcases.co.uk (or any website linked from samcases.co.uk) may be limited for purely technical reasons and you may not be able to purchase products.
If you have chosen to restrict, block or delete cookies from samcases.co.uk, you will still be able to browse the website, search for products and services and read content, but some functions may become unavailable either now or in the future. You may block cookies, or delete existing cookies, by adjusting the appropriate setting in your browser. Each browser is different, so please check its "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookies preferences. For more information on this, visit www.allaboutcookies.org
Links to Other Websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Data aggregation, analytics and profile creation
We may analyse your browsing behaviour to draw inferences and create profiles about your personal preferences and behaviours. We may then use such information for the purposes described below:
(a) Served by us - We may use your information (including profile data) to serve you with advertising, which is relevant to you, on our websites and the websites of third parties.
(b) Served by third parties on our websites - Advertisers or other third parties using our website may also engage in behavioural advertising and use cookies and web beacons in the manner described above. We do not control these advertisers or other parties' use of cookies or web beacons or what they do with the information they collect.
(c) Served by third parties on third party websites - We may provide your personal information (including profile data) to third parties who may then use it in combination with personal information that they have collected from you to serve you with relevant advertising on third party websites.
Controlling your Personal Information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
If you have any questions relating to our Privacy Policy please contact us
Why not share your requirements with us by completing our quote request form.
Get a FREE Quote
